<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2016-2017 Projekt Substratum
  ~ This file is part of Substratum.
  ~
  ~ Substratum is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ Substratum is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~ GNU General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
  ~ along with Substratum.  If not, see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="question_one">What is Substratum?</string>
    <string name="answer_one">Substratum is an app that takes advantage of Sony\'s Overlay Manager
        Service (OMS). This is similar to Layers in terms of stability and customization (as it
        builds off RRO) but features such things as no reboots to apply, boot animations, fonts and
        priority switching.
    </string>

    <string name="question_two">What is the Theme Interfacer?</string>
    <string name="answer_two">The Theme Interfacer is the base of what allows Substratum to run
        like a Theme Engine. The idea of an interface is to simulate the “server/client”
        technicalities and Substratum communicates with the Interface handlers to signal commands
        directly on the system.
    </string>

    <string name="question_three">What do I need in order for Substratum to work properly?</string>
    <string name="answer_three">You will need a ROM that has support for the OMS and Theme Interface
        system (ask them, they will know), this app, and a compatible theme (check its
        Play Store description or ask the developer)
    </string>

    <string name="question_four">Can I use Substratum even if my ROM does not have OMS support?
    </string>
    <string name="answer_four">Yes, if your ROM has support for RRO (stock Marshmallow falls into
        the category). The other requirements above are the same (root, this app, and a compatible
        theme). You will apply the same way but the compilation and apply steps are combined and a
        reboot is required to apply the overlays.
    </string>

    <string name="question_five">How do I apply a theme?</string>
    <string name="answer_five">The application of a theme is a two part process: compilation of the
        overlays and application of the overlays. If you want to compile and apply in one step, use
        the Quick Apply tab and choose one or both of the options. If you want to compile then
        apply, go into the theme, click the Overlay Manager tab, select the overlays and options you
        want, hit the FAB and choose Compile/Update, then chose those same overlays, and hit the FAB
        and choose Enable Selected.
    </string>

    <string name="question_six">My overlays did not compile, what happened?</string>
    <string name="answer_six">Delete your /system/bin/aopt file, relaunch the application, and try
        the above process again.
    </string>

    <string name="question_seven">My theme did not apply, what happened?</string>
    <string name="answer_seven">If you are applying a theme for the first time or from the stock
        theme, make sure you do not have the \"Disable other themes\" option checked.
    </string>

    <string name="question_eight">I\'m bootlooping! How do I fix it?</string>
    <string name="answer_eight">Substratum has it\'s own recovery system called Substratum Rescue
        System (SRS), which is an automated system that dumps an archive into
        /storage/emulated/0/substratum/SubstratumRescue.zip. Flash this ZIP in recovery and reboot!
    </string>

    <string name="question_nine">Some elements look janky after I applied a theme, what happened?
    </string>
    <string name="answer_nine">
        1. Restart SystemUI if it didn\'t do so automatically.\n2. Reboot the phone.\n3. Unapply
        and/or delete the overlays, recompile, and reapply.
    </string>

    <string name="question_ten">Where are overlays installed?</string>
    <string name="answer_ten">Overlays are installed in the /data/app folder, which means each
        overlay getting its own folder.
    </string>

    <string name="question_eleven">I\'m getting an error when trying to update a theme on the Play
        Store.
    </string>
    <string name="answer_eleven">Uninstall the theme and reinstall it.</string>

    <string name="question_twelve">Who do I contact if I have a serious issue not resolved by
        reading these steps?
    </string>
    <string name="answer_twelve">Please make a post in the Substratum Google+ community. Please provide
        the following information: Substratum version, ROM, theme (if issues applying one), and, if
        possible, a logcat.
    </string>

</resources>
