<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="question_one">What is Substratum?</string>
    <string name="answer_one">Substratum is an app that takes advantage of Sony\'s Overlay Manager Service (OMS). This is similar to Layers in terms of stability and customization (as it builds off RRO) but features such things as no reboots to apply, boot animations, fonts and priority switching.</string>

    <string name="question_two">What is the Masquerade System?</string>
    <string name="answer_two">The Masquerade System is the base of what allows Substratum to run like a Theme Engine. The idea of a masquerade is to simulate the “server/client” technicalities and Substratum communicates with the Masquerade handlers to signal commands directly on the system.</string>

    <string name="question_three">What do I need in order for Substratum to work properly?</string>
    <string name="answer_three">You will need a ROM that has support for the OMS and Masquerade system (ask them, they will know), root access, this app, and a compatible theme (check its Play Store description or ask the developer)</string>

    <string name="question_four">Can I use Substratum even if my ROM does not have OMS support?</string>
    <string name="answer_four">Yes, if your ROM has support for RRO (stock Marshmallow falls into the category). The other requirements above are the same (root, this app, and a compatible theme). You will apply the same way but the compilation and apply steps are combined and a reboot is required to apply the overlays.</string>

    <string name="question_five">How do I apply a theme?</string>
    <string name="answer_five">The application of a theme is a two part process: compilation of the overlays and application of the overlays. If you want to compile and apply in one step, use the Quick Apply tab and choose one or both of the options. If you want to compile then apply, go into the theme, click the Overlay Manager tab, select the overlays and options you want, hit the FAB and choose Compile/Update, then chose those same overlays, and hit the FAB and choose Enable Selected.</string>

    <string name="question_six">My overlays did not compile, what happened?</string>
    <string name="answer_six">Delete your /system/bin/aapt file, relaunch the application, and try the above process again.</string>

    <string name="question_seven">My theme did not apply, what happened?</string>
    <string name="answer_seven">If you are applying a theme for the first time or from the stock theme, make sure you do not have the Disable other themes option checked.</string>

    <string name="question_eight">I\'m bootlooping! How do I fix it?</string>
    <string name="answer_eight">Delete the file /data/system/overlays.xml in TWRP\'s file manager or adb shell and reboot. Additionally, if you have security set up on your phone, you will need to delete the /data/resource-cache folder.</string>

    <string name="question_nine">Some elements look janky after I applied a theme, what happened?</string>
    <string name="answer_nine">
        1. Restart SystemUI if it didn\'t do so automatically.\n2. Reboot the phone.\n3. Unapply and/or delete the overlays, recompile, and reapply.
    </string>

    <string name="question_ten">Where are overlays installed?</string>
    <string name="answer_ten">Overlays are installed in the /data/app folder, which means each overlay getting its own folder.</string>

    <string name="question_eleven">I\'m getting an error when trying to update a theme on the Play Store.</string>
    <string name="answer_eleven">Uninstall the theme and reinstall it.</string>

    <string name="question_twelve">Who do I contact if I have a serious issue not resolved by reading these steps?</string>
    <string name="answer_twelve">Please make a post in the BitSyko Google+ community. Please provide the following information: Substratum version, ROM, theme (if issues applying one), and, if possible, a logcat.</string>

</resources>